flashingjungle.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Nude in public flashing pics Upskirt No panties Boobs flash Dick flash photos Public nudity Voyeur Public sex from Tumblr, Google, Pinterest, Facebook, Snapchat, Instagram and Twitter

## Privacy Policy

FlashingJungle.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Contact us at if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.

By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Table of Contents

  1. Definitions used in this Policy
  2. Data protection principles we follow
  3. What rights do you have regarding your Personal Data
  4. What Personal Data we gather about you
  5. How we use your Personal Data
  6. Who else has access to your Personal Data
  7. How we secure your data
  8. Information about cookies
  9. Contact information

**Personal Data**  – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.  
**Processing**  – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data.  
**Data subject**  – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed.  
**Child** – a natural person under 16 years of age.  
**We/us** (either capitalized or not) –

We promise to follow the following data protection principles:

  * Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.
  * Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.
  * Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.
  * Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.
  * We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.
  * We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.

The Data Subject has the following rights:

  1. Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.
  2. Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.
  3. Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  4. Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.
  5. Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.
  6. Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.
  7. Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.
  8. Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.
  9. Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us.
  10. Right for the help of supervisory authority – meaning you have the right for the help of a supervisory authority and the right for other legal remedies such as claiming damages.
  11. Right to withdraw consent – you have the right withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.

**Information you have provided us with**  
We save the information you provide us with in order for you to comment or perform other activities on the website. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.

**Information automatically collected about you**  
This includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your IP address, browsing history (if there is any) etc. This information is used to improve your customer experience. When you  look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged.

**Information from our partners**  
We gather information from our trusted partners with confirmation that they have legal grounds to share that information with us. This is either information you have provided them directly with or that they have gathered about you on other legal grounds. See the list of our partners here.

**Publicly available information**  
We might gather information about you that is publicly available.

We use your Personal Data in order to:

  * provide our service to you. This includes for example registering your account; communicating and interacting with you; and notifying you of changes to any services.
  * enhance your browsing experience;
  * fulfil an obligation under law or contract;

On the ground of legitimate interest, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to administer and analyse our client base in order to improve the quality of website;
  * to conduct questionnaires concerning client satisfaction;

As long as you have not informed us otherwise, we consider offering you content that are similar or same to your browsing behavior to be our legitimate interest.

With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to send you newsletters and campaign offers (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);
  * for other purposes we have asked your consent for;

We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfill obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymise Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymised. We save information gathered about you for as long as needed for any obligations deriving from law, but not longer than 2 years.

We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:

  * the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;
  * the further Processing would not harm your interests
  * there would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.

We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.

We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. We disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it.

We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymising and pseudonymising where suitable. We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks.

Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.

If you have an account with us, note that you have to keep your username and password secret.

### Children

We do not intend to collect or knowingly collect information from children. We do not target children with our services.

We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.

A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.

**We use cookies for the following purposes:**

  * Necessary cookies – these cookies are required for you to be able to use some important features on our website, such as logging in. These cookies don’t collect any personal information.
  * Functionality cookies – these cookies provide functionality that makes using our service more convenient and makes providing more personalised features possible. For example, they might remember your name and e-mail in comment forms so you don’t have to re-enter this information next time when commenting.
  * Analytics cookies – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services
  * Advertising cookies – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

You can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/) or [youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). For more information about cookies, visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

By accessing and viewing this site, **you acknowledge that you have read and understood these Legal Terms of Service**. These terms can be modified by us at any time without notice.

**Automatic Logging:**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and IP address to diagnose problems with our server and help identify you for on-line voting.  
**Cookies:**  
We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, target ads, and help identify you for on-line voting.  
**Use of Information:**  
Information collected by the server through cookies and other means will not be shared with anyone for any purpose. The sole purpose of it is to improve the site’s operations and content.  
**External Links:**  
This site contains links to other sites. FlashingJungle.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.  
**Contacts:**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site feel free to contact us [HERE](mailto:webmaster@flashingjungle.com)

We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.  
Last modification was made May 29th 2018.
